<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bhojan</string>
    <string name="app_name_extended">Bhojan</string>
    <string name="hey_there">Namaste 🙏</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_bhojan">Welcome to\nBhojan!</string>
    <string name="continue_with_google">  Continue with Google</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="more">More</string>
    <string name="a_simple_banana">a simple banana</string>
    <string name="a_simple_lemonslice">a simple lemonslice</string>
    <string name="share_a_meal">Share-a-Meal 🍲</string>
    <string name="name_of_food">Enter Name of the Food Item</string>
    <string name="key_details">Some Key Ingredients Go Here…</string>
    <string name="suggestions">Any Suggestions for the Food?</string>
    <string name="share_food">Share Food</string>
    <string name="image_to_be_uploaded">Image to be uploaded</string>
    <string name="tips">Hmm…there is no internet right now, but food might be.\nDo share it if excess!</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string-array name="greetings">
        <item>Hello</item>
        <item>नमस्ते</item>
        <item>Hola</item>
        <item>Olá</item>
        <item>こんにちは</item>
        <item>你好</item>
        <item>Salve</item>
        <item>హలో</item>
        <item>안녕하세요</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="button_START">Begin</string>
    <string name="button_Guides">Guide</string>
    <string name="button_Credits">Credits</string>
    <string name="button_Quit">Back to Bhojan</string>
    <string name="developed_by">Developed by:</string>
    <string name="developer_name">Ali Elganzory</string>
    <string name="linkedin">LinkedIn</string>
    <string name="linkedin_link">linkedin.com/in/AliElganzory</string>
    <string name="b_Call">Call</string>
    <string name="support">Support:</string>
    <string name="laptop">Laptop</string>
    <string name="bed">Bed</string>
    <string name="Menu_Title">fly FOOd</string>
    <string name="a_flying_food">Flying food</string>
    <string name="Start_Score">0</string>
    <string name="GO_replay">Again</string>
    <string name="GO_menu">Home</string>
    <string name="target_view">Target</string>
    <string name="High_Score">High-score:</string>
    <string name="menu_high_score">0</string>
    <string name="fullTime">90</string>
    <string name="TimerTitle">Time:</string>
    <string name="about_developers">About Developers</string>
    <string name="system">System</string>
    <string name="light">Light</string>
    <string name="dark">Dark</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_text"><b>Summary of Privacy Policy of Bhojan</b>\n\nWe take your right to privacy very seriously and so before you download the BHOJAN app, please take a few moments to read how we collect and use your data.\n\n You can also read our full Privacy Policy below.\nWhy we need your data We need to collect this information about you when you sign up and each time you use the app so that you can get the most out of BHOJAN.\n• We do not collect sensitive information such as any medical details. • We store your personal information carefully. You have consented to provide this information to us but can withdraw your consent at any time by getting in touch with us (connectwithspandan@gmail.com). What we do with your data We retain personal information only for as long as necessary to carry out these functions. If you notify us that you no longer wish to be listed on the database we will delete your information as soon as possible. • We use your location data to provide information to you about items available nearby. • We do not share your information with anyone unless we are required to do so by law or it is necessary to make the app run properly. • We do not sell your information to anyone. All the personal data we process is located on Google Firebase. What are your rights? You have a right to see the information we hold on you and/or require your data to be deleted by making a request in writing to the email address below. If at any point you believe the information we process on you is incorrect you can request to have it corrected. If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal data, you can contact us and we will investigate the matter. • You can adjust your preferences by denying the location permission from the App Settings any time. • You can request access to your information or ask us to delete it by contacting us. If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are processing your personal data not in accordance with the law you can complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO). If you agree to the above, download the app. If you do not agree or would like some further information then please contact us at connectwithspandan@gmail.com PRIVACY POLICY Last updated: April 14, 2021 1. Introduction 1.1 One Silicon Diode respects your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This policy describes: • The identity of the data controller. • What personal data is collected including the types of information we may collect or that you may provide when you download, access or use the BHOJAN app (the “App“). Note: for the purposes of this policy both the website www.BHOJANex.com and the BHOJAN application shall be referred to as the “App”. • How personal data is collected. • Why personal data is collected. • How we use personal data. • How personal data is shared and with whom. • What choices you have with respect to how personal data is used. • How long personal data is kept. • Your rights with respect to personal data. 1.2 This policy applies only to information we collect in the App, via e-mail, text and other electronic communications sent through or in connection with the App This policy DOES NOT apply to information that: • We collect offline or on any other Company apps or websites. • You provide to or is collected by any third party (see “THIRD-PARTY INFORMATION COLLECTION” (unless this information is provided by them to us)). 1.3 Please note, we may have a separate privacy policy for our other websites and apps and third parties may have their own privacy policies, which we encourage you to read before providing information on or through them. 1.4 Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. A SUMMARY OF THIS POLICY IS ALSO AVAILABLE. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, do not download, register with or use this App. By downloading, registering with or using this App and, where applicable, ticking our consent boxes, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see “CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY”). Unless such changes mean changes to your preferences, your continued use of this App after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates. 1.5 Users under the Age of 18: We do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under 18. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from anyone under 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information if requested. If you believe we might have any information from or about a user under 18, please contact us at: connectwithspandan@gmail.com Identity of Data Controller 2.1 We collect information from and about users of our App: • Directly from you when you provide it to us. • Automatically when you use the App. 2.2 We do not collect special categories of personal data such as information relating to or about the below or information about criminal records. • Health • Racial or ethnic origin • Political opinions • Membership of a political association, professional or trade association • Membership of a trade union • Religious beliefs or affiliations • Philosophical beliefs • Sexual orientation or practices • Biometric information 2.3 Information that you provide to us (“personal information”) when you download, register with or use this App may include: • First Name, Last Name; • Postal address; • E-mail address; and • Profile picture. 2.4 In addition we may collect other information that is about you but individually does not identify you, such as age or gender. 2.5 This information may also include: • Information that you provide by signing in the App such as first name, last name, email address, and address (after sharing something). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use the App and requesting further services. • We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, such as your Contact Information. • Information you provide to us when you complete user surveys or surveys for research purposes such as your Contact Information. • Information you provide to us when you report a problem with the App such as your first name, last name and email address. • Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses and phone numbers), if you contact us. • Details of transactions you carry out through the App and of the fulfilment of your orders. • Your correspondence within the App with other users (your username and location). 2.6 Third-party Information Collection 2.6.1 When you use the App or its content, certain third parties may use automatic information collection technologies to collect information about you or your device. These third parties may include: • Analytics companies. • Your mobile device manufacturer. • Your mobile service provider. 2.6.2 These third parties may use tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use the App. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites, apps and other online services or websites. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioural) advertising or other targeted content. 2.6.3 We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. 2.6.4 For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see “CHOICES ABOUT HOW WE USE AND DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION”. How personal data is collected. 3.1 Automatic Information Collection and Tracking. 3.1.1 When you download, access and use the App, it may use technology to automatically collect: • Usage Details. When you access and use the App, we may automatically collect certain details of your access to and use of the App, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on or through the App. • Device Information. We may collect information about your mobile device and internet connection, including the device’s unique device identifier, IP address, operating system, browser type, mobile network information and the device’s telephone number. • Stored Information and Files. The App also may access metadata and other information associated with other files stored on your device. This may include, for example, photographs you share. You will be asked for your consent to such access and use of your personal data within the App. You can withdraw your consent at any time via the settings menu. • Location Information. This App collects real-time information about the location of your device. We do not, however, continually collect user location data nor do we collect location data without the user being aware. We store the location of a user at set points for example when you choose to update your location and when you create an item. Some of our location-enabled Services require your personal data for the feature to work. You will be asked for your consent to such access and use of your personal data within the App. Note, however, that opting out of the App’s collection of location information will cause its location-based features to be disabled. You can withdraw your consent at any time via the app settings menu. 3.2 If you do not want us to collect this information, please do not create an account with us. 3.3 We may also use these technologies to collect information about your activities over time and across third-party websites, apps or other online services (behavioural tracking). 3.4 Information Collection and Tracking Technologies. 3.4.1 The technologies we use for automatic information collection may include: 3.5 Third Party Software/Services 4.5.1 We use the following third party software/services to collect and process your personal data for the following reasons: • Google Fire services including Crashlytics. How we use personal data and lawful bases for processing 4.1 Lawful Bases for Processing under the GDPR What are the lawful bases for processing personal data? The lawful bases for processing are set out in Article 6 of the GDPR. At least one of these must apply whenever we process personal data. We mainly use consent, contract, legal obligations and legitimate interests as the bases to process your personal data in accordance with this privacy policy. 1. Consent: the individual has given clear consent for us to process their personal data for a specific purpose. 2. Contract: the processing is necessary for a contract we have with the individual, or because they have asked us to take specific steps before entering into a contract. 3. Legal obligation: the processing is necessary for us to comply with the law (not including contractual obligations). 4. Legitimate interests: the processing is necessary for our legitimate interests or the legitimate interests of a third party unless there is a good reason to protect the individual’s personal data which overrides those legitimate interests. 5.1 The usage information we collect helps us to improve our App and to deliver a better and more personalised experience by enabling us to: • Estimate our audience size and usage patterns (such processing is necessary for our legitimate interests (for running our services and to study how users use our App). • Speed up your searches (such processing is necessary for our legitimate interests (for running our services). • Recognise you when you use the App (such processing is necessary for the performance of our contract). • To provide us with information about how the App is running or whether there are any faults or issues with our products and services (such processing is necessary for our legitimate interests (for us to deliver a better service to you). 5.2 We use location data for the following reasons: • To provide information about food or non-food items within a fixed distance from the user’s set location (such information is necessary for the performance of our contract with you). • To allow others to receive information about a user’s food or non-food items within their search radius (such information is necessary for the performance of our contract with you). 5.3 We have implemented reasonable measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorised access, use, alteration and disclosure. Changes to Our Privacy Policy 6.1 We may update our privacy policy from time to time. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will post the new privacy policy on this page with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated. 6.2 The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for periodically visiting this privacy policy to check for any changes. 7 Contact Information 7.1 All questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy should be addressed to the contact details as set out in the App and on e-mail to connectwithspandan@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="by_tapping_continue_you_agree_to_the_terms_and_conditions_laid_down_by_bhojan">By tapping \'Continue\' you agree to the Privacy Policy laid down by Bhojan.</string>
    <string name="just_before_we_begin">Just Before We Begin</string>
    <string name="goAhead">Continue</string>
    <string name="we_need_to_access_your_location_before_bhojan_can_start_so_that_the_food_you_share_can_be_located_by_the_one_in_need_provide_location_permission_to_continue_using_bhojan">We need to access your location before Bhojan can start, so that the food you share can be located by the one in need.\n\nProvide Location Permission to continue using Bhojan</string>
</resources>